McKersie, Robert Research Collection for "The Impact of Collective Bargaining on Management" 6326
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert McKersie Research Collection for "The Impact of Collective Bargaining on Management"
1967-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKersie, Robert
Brookings Institute
Slichter, Sumner H.
Healy, James J.
Livernash, E. Robert
6326
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7506529
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; McKersie, Robert B.
7506529
- Reports (Box 1)
  - Brookings Topics Administration of Union-Management Contracts (574) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brookings Topics. Assignment of Works (569) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brookings Topics Arbitration (516) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brooking Topics. Communications (608) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brookings Topics. Discipline (496) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brookings Topics. Grievance Machinery (309), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brookings Topics. Grievance Adjustment (340) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brooking Topics, High Cost Plants (511), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brooking Topics Hiring Control of (587), 1924-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brookings Topics. Hiring, Controls of (Maritime) (623), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brooking Topics. Interview Material (453), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brookings Topics Negotiations (563) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Brookings Topics. Restrictive for Practices (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Brookings Topics. Restrictive for Practices (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brookings Topic. Restricting for Practices (549) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brookings Topics. Strikes (543), 1949-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brookings Topics. Strikes (copy 2) (543) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Brookings Topics. Strikes, Additions (543) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Brookings Topics. Subcontracting (505), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Brookings Topics, Wage Structures (581), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Brookings Topics. Union Policies (531), 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brookings Topics. Unions and Technological Change (342) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brookings Topics. Wage Structures (581), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Brookings Topics. Wage Structure Considerations (604) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pensions Current News, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Pensions. Disability Retirement in Industrial Pensions Plans, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Pensions. Handbook on Pensions, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Pensions. Hanover Pension Bulletin, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Health and Welfare Plans in NYC, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pensions. Medical Health and Hospital Service of the Welfare and Retirement Fund of the UMW, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Pensions Paid Vacation Provisions in Major Union Contracts, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Pensions. Pension Plans Under Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pensions. Selective Retirement and Pre-Retirement Counseling in the TVA, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Pensions. A Study of Industrial Retirement Plans, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Pensions. Time Off With Pay, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Railroads. Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Railroads. Force Reduction (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Railroads Major Cities with or without Rail Service (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Railroads. National Mediation Board Rules (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Railroads. Railway Labor Act, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Railroads Railroad Shop Craft Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Railroads, Railroads Which Would Not be Struck (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Railroads, Report to the President by the Emergency Board No. 169, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Railroads, Report by the Special Panel, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Railroads, Donald J. White, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Railroads, Donald J. White, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)